infomediainc.com 2009-02-28

# Infomedia Inc Privacy Policy

This is the web site of InfoMedia, Inc.

Our postal address is: 1151 Eagle Drive, Suite 325, Loveland, CO 80537-8020. We can be reached via our [ Support Desk](http://support.infomediainc.com/). Or you can reach us by telephone at (970) 278-0011.

The policies below are applicable to worldvillage.com, toylab.com, dealofday.com, freebietracker.com, familyfirst.com and other sites on the World Wide Web portion of the Internet owned and operated by InfoMedia, Inc. 

InfoMedia, Inc. collects personally identifying information only during (i) contest or sweepstakes Registration, (ii) subscription Registration for sites that require subscription, (iii) opt-in email lists where content is specifically presented, and (iv) online shopping. In addition, Registration is required and information is collected in certain portions of sites in which guests provide content submissions and suggestions or participate in interactive online activities (i.e., community postings, voting, chat, games, or bulletin boards). InfoMedia, Inc. may use such information to fulfill prizes, track compliance with our House Rules, or for editorial and feedback purposes (to the extent that is explained when guests provide the information). In the event that InfoMedia, Inc. plans to post any such information on a site, guests are provided prior notification of such posting and given the option of preventing such posting. 

**   
Policies for Individuals Under 13**

InfoMedia, Inc. encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the interactive activities offered on the sites.

No information should be submitted to or posted at InfoMedia, Inc.’s Web sites by guests under 13 years of age without the consent of their parent or guardian. 

Unless otherwise disclosed during collection, InfoMedia, Inc. does not provide any personally identifying information, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever.

No information collected from guests under 13 years of age is used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever, either inside or outside InfoMedia, Inc. 

Guests’ e-mail addresses are never posted on InfoMedia, Inc. Web sites, except where a guest uses our message boards. The Guest has an option to have his or her email address appear. 

**Policies for Individuals 13 Years of Age or Older**

With the permission of a guest who is 13 years of age or over, information submitted at the time of Registration or submission may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by InfoMedia, Inc. and may be shared with our affiliates or companies that have been prescreened by InfoMedia, Inc.. If a guest objects to such use for any reason, he/she may stop that use by e-mail request. Once you have registered with InfoMedia, Inc., every effort will be made to maintain your information in a secure environment by InfoMedia, Inc. and our affiliates. 

If you wish to modify your Registration information or stop receiving e-mail updates from InfoMedia, Inc., just send an email request to [Support Desk](http://support.infomediainc.com/).

**About IP Addresses**

InfoMedia, Inc. collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers.

An IP address is a number that’s automatically assigned to your computer whenever you’re surfing the Web. Web servers -- the big computers that "serve" up Web pages -- automatically identify your computer by its IP address.

When guests request pages from InfoMedia, Inc. sites, our servers log the guests’ IP addresses. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user’s session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us.

**Us** **e of Cookies**

What are cookies? Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make Web-surfing easier for you by saving your passwords, purchases, and preferences while you’re at our site. The use of cookies is an Industry standard -- you’ll find them at most major Web sites.

By showing how and when guests use the site, cookies help us see which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. If you accept the first tracking cookie from any InfoMedia, Inc. web site, you won’t be offered as many afterwards.

**Examples of How InfoMedia, Inc. Sites Use Cookies**

A cookie lets the computers remember that you’ve registered, which allows us to speed up your future activities at our sites. Similarly, The WorldVillage Store Online uses a temporary cookie to track which products you’ve chosen while shopping. The cookie expires once you’re done shopping. Letting it do the record keeping saves you the trouble of entering information over and over again during a single visit. If you decline this cookie, you may have difficulty ordering your selections. 

**How InfoMedia, Inc. Sites Do Not Use Cookies**

InfoMedia, Inc. sites never use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. Except as described below, InfoMedia, Inc. sites do not use information transferred through cookies for any promotional or marketing purposes, nor is that information shared with any third parties whatsoever. 

InfoMedia, Inc. sites do not use cookies to identify specific individuals, except in such cases as online shopping (see above) and contest registration (where a cookie allows you to enter a contest every day without registering again each time).

You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers. InfoMedia, Inc. does not control these cookies, and these cookies are not subject to the InfoMedia, Inc. cookie policy. The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you’d prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, it is possible that some parts of the site, such as the shopping, contest, and game areas, will not function properly if you do so.

**Links to Other Sites**

Users should be aware that when you are on InfoMedia, Inc. sites you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from InfoMedia, Inc. sites that take you outside our service. For example, if you click on a banner advertisement or a InfoMedia, Inc. search result, the click takes you off the InfoMedia, Inc. site. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors, and partners that may use InfoMedia, Inc.’s logo as part of a cobranding agreement. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. Always be aware of where you end up.

Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online – for example, via message boards or chat – that information can be collected and used by people you don’t know. While InfoMedia, Inc. strives to protect its users’ personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online, and you do so at your own risk.

This site uses the services of Tribal Fusion for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To do this, Tribal Fusion collects anonymous data typically through the use of cookies. To learn more about Tribal Fusion, including your ability to opt out of the Tribal Fusion system, go to [Tribal Fusion](http://www.tribalfusion.com/).

Your Acceptance of These Terms By using this site, you signify your assent to the InfoMedia, Inc. Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our sites. Your continued use of the InfoMedia, Inc. sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. You can send e-mail to us with any further questions.
